A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Near & Middle East, Record Group 3, Series 9 FA1777
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East, 1959-1996; 1; 26.06 Cubic Feet 66 containers
  - Cole, Juan - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 331)
  - Combs-Schilling, Elaine - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 332)
  - Fawaz, Leila - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 333)
  - Fleisher, Cornell - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 334)
  - Karpat, Kemal H. - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 335)
  - Lockman, Zachary - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 336)
  - Petreet, Julie M. - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 337)
  - Phillipp, Thomas - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 338)
  - Quataert, Donald - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1986 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 339)
  - Singer, Amy - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1986 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 340)
  - Landis, Joshua - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1986 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 341)
  - Reynolds, Dwight - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1986 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 342)
  - Blankinship, Khalid - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1985 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 343)
  - Lowi, Miriam - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1985 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1985-1990 (Box 40, Folder 344)
  - Batatu, Hanna - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 345)
  - Botman, Selma - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral, 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 346)
  - Brown, Leon - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 347)
  - Findley, Carter V. - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 348)
  - Cooke, Miriam - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 349)
  - Goffman, Daniel - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 350)
  - Hinnebusch, Raymond A. - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1985-1989 (Box 40, Folder 351)
  - Pamuk, Sevet - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1987 (Box 40, Folder 352)
  - Rosenfeld, Henry - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 353)
  - Wakin, Jeanette - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1985 - Postdoctoral Award, 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 354)
  - Spellberg, Denise A. - Near and Middle East interntational Dissertation Fellowship 1984 - Predoctoral Award, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 355)
  - Swedenburg, Theodore R. - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1984 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 356)
  - Russell, Sharon S. - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1984 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1984-1985 (Box 41, Folder 357)
  - Bisharat, George E. - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1983 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1985 (Box 41, Folder 358)
  - Guhl, Nora - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1983 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 359)
  - Haj (Abuel), Samira - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1983 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1982-1987 (Box 41, Folder 360)
  - Marefat, Mina - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1983 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 361)
  - Pandolfo, Stefania - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1984 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 362)
  - Reilly, James - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1984 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 363)
  - Assad, Ragui - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1991 (Box 42, Folder 364)
  - Matthee, Rudolph - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 365)
  - Landis, Joshua - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 366)
  - Bellin, Eva - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 367)
  - Accad, Evelyne - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1990 (Box 42, Folder 368)
  - Al-Imad, Leila - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 369)
  - Kerr, John - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 370)
  - Brumberg, Daniel - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1988 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 371)
  - Posusney, Marsha - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1986-1992 (Box 42, Folder 372)
  - Ruggles, D. Fairchild - Near and Middle East International Doctoral Research 1987 Fellowship - Predoctoral, 1987-1989 (Box 42, Folder 373)
  - Tabak, Faruk - Near and Middle East Fellowship Award 1987 - Predoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 374)
  - Badran, Margot - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 375)
  - Daly, Martin - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 376)
  - Haeri, Shahla - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 377)
  - Harik, Iliya - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 378)
  - Clement, Henry - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 379)
  - Hunter, Robert - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 380)
  - Kay, Paul - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 381)
  - Shaban, Radwan - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 382)
  - Near and Middle East - Fellowship Grant Materials, 1985-1987 (Box 43, Folder 383)
  - Yeshilda, Birol - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 384)
  - Allen, Terry - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 385)
  - Abou-El-Haj, Rifa'at Ali - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1987 - Postdoctoral, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 386)
  - Munson, Henry - Near and Middle East Research Grant 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 387)
  - Moaddel, Mansoor - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 388)
  - Lindisfarne, Nancy - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 389)
  - Farazmand, Ali - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 390)
  - Frierson, Elizabeth - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 391)
  - Ghazzal, Zouhair A. - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 392)
  - Gulalp, Haldun - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 393)
  - Hunter, Frederick R. - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 394)
  - Katz, Sheila - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 395)
  - Lemel, Harold - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 396)
  - Lowi, Miriam - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 397)
  - Mitchell, Edward - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 398)
  - Peled, Alisa R. - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 399)
  - Shields, Sarah - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 400)
  - Sikainga, Ahmad - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 401)
  - Thompson, John - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 402)
  - Vander Lippe, John - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 403)
  - Zouari, Jawed - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 404)
  - Segal, Jerome - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 405)
  - Shafir, Gershon - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 406)
  - Soofi, Abdol - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 407)
  - Souffrant, Eddy - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 408)
  - Schilcher, Linda - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 409)
  - Danesh, Abol H. - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 410)
  - Accad, Evelyne - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 411)
  - Anscombe, Frederick - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 412)
  - Baykan, Aysegul - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 413)
  - Calabrese, John - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 414)
  - Carkoglu, Ali - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 415)
  - Duben, Alan - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 416)
  - Danesh, Abol H. - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 417)
  - Gallagher, Sally - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 418)
  - Goode, Erich - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 419)
  - Hosseinzadeh, Esmial - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 420)
  - Khaldieh, Salim - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 421)
  - Larkin, Margaret - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 422)
  - Rouse, Shahnaz - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 423)
  - Sohrabi, Nader - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 424)
  - Bayat, Mangol - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 425)
  - Near and Middle East Grant and Fellowship Application Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 426)
  - Izady, Mehrdad - Near and Middle East Grant - Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 427)
  - Bonner, Michael D. - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 428)
  - Addi, Lahouari - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 429)
  - Ali Musa, El Khider - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 430)
  - Howard, Douglas - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 431)
  - Altaie, Ali - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 432)
  - Haj, Samira - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 433)
  - Kurzman, Charles - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 434)
  - Lindisfarne, Nancy - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 435)
  - Lubling, Yoram - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 436)
  - McHenry, Stewart - Near and Middle East Fellowship Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 437)
  - Mutzner, Melvin - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 438)
  - Solingen, Etel - Near and Middle East Grant Declination - Postdoctoral, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 439)
  - Near and Middle East Fellows - Transcripts, 1984-1990 (Box 77, Folder 787-789)
    Restricted - Student Records
  - Datasheets and Transcripts, 1982-1986 (Box 77, Folder 790)
  - Workshop on "Law, Property, and State Power," Istanbul, Turkey, 1992 September 10-11 (Box 46, Folder 440)
  - Meeting Agendas, 1988-1993 (Box 46, Folder 441-448, Box 47, Folder 449-454, Box 48, Folder 455)
  - Workshop Materials - Comparative and Area Studies, 1981-1988 (Box 48, Folder 456)
  - Questions of Modernity Planning Proposal, 1989-1992 (Box 48, Folder 457)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Comparative Perspectives on the Family in the Middle East, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 458)
  - Ottoman Political Reform in the Provinces: The Case of the Damascus Advisory Council in 1844-45, Elizabeth Thompson, undated (Box 48, Folder 459)
  - Bridging the Divide Workshop, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 460)
  - Transnational Planning Meetings, 1981-1990 (Box 48, Folder 461)
  - Questions of Modernity Meeting, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 462)
  - Political Economy Workshop, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 463)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 464)
  - Transnational and Comparative Working Group, 1990-1991 (Box 49, Folder 465)
  - Transnational and Comparative Research, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 466)
  - Meeting of the Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East - Agenda, 1989 March-1991 March (Box 49, Folder 467-469)
  - Ibn Khaldun Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 56, Folder 542-543, Box 57, Folder 544-547)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Cairo Participants' Reports, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 548, Box 58, Folder 549)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Cairo Participant - Stevenson, Thomas B., 1982 (Box 58, Folder 550)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East Inquiries, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 551)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure of the Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East Meeting - Minutes, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 552)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 553)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure Meeting of the Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 554)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure of the Joint Committee on the Near and Middle East Meeting - Minutes, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 554-555)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure Conference on Family, Law and Change in the Contemporary Near and Middle East (Amal Rassam), 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 556)
  - Conference on Social Legislation in the Contemporary Near and Middle East, Rabat, Morocco, 1981-1983 (Box 58, Folder 557)
  - Volume: Property, Social Structure, and Law in the Modern Middle East (Ann Mayer) - Transfer of Rights Letters, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 558)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East Meeting - Agenda Materials, 1983 February 12 (Box 58, Folder 559)
  - Memos to Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 560)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Funding Proposal for Phase II, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 561)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure in the Middle East - Acceptances, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 562)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure - Mailing, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 563)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure - Applicants, undated (Box 58, Folder 564)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure - Syllabus, 1969-1981 (Box 58, Folder 565)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure - Travel Information, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 566)
  - Ibn Khaldun Prize Papers and Rankings, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 567)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Minutes and Agenda Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 568-569)
  - Social Legislation in the Contemporary Middle East, Rabat, Morocco - Conference and Volume, 1981-1984 (Box 59, Folder 570-571)
  - Reports to United States Agency for International Development - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure Project, 1979-1983 (Box 59, Folder 572)
  - United States Agency for International Development Grant Documents - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure, 1978-1983 (Box 59, Folder 573)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure in the Near and Middle East - Conferences, 1980-1981 (Box 59, Folder 574)
  - Conference on Social Legislation and Social Structure in the Contemporary Near and Middle East, Rabat, Morocco - Original Papers, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 575-576)
  - Summer Institute on Law and Social Structure - Administration, 1979-1983 (Box 60, Folder 577)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Akan, Vildan, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 578)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Al-Awadhi, Badria, 1981-1982 (Box 60, Folder 579)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Ben Achour, Rafaa - Declined, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 580)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Bisharat, George E., 1979-1982 (Box 60, Folder 581)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Ebersole, Jon M., 1982 (Box 60, Folder 582)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Hamid, Hamid Awad, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 583)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Kadouf, Hunud, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 584)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Forrest, Nazan, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 585)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Makdisi, John, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 586)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Mathews, Marilynn, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 587)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Molyneaux, Sylvia, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 588)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Peteet, Julie, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 589)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Invitation - Zikry, Sanna, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 590)
  - Subcommittee on Law and Social Structure - Summer Institute Participants, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 591)
  - Law and Society Articles, 1968-1979 (Box 60, Folder 592, Box 61, Folder 593)
  - Law Training Fellowship Program File - Musa Adam Abdul-Jalil, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 594)
  - Law Training Fellowship Program File - M. Nour Farahat, 1982-1983 (Box 61, Folder 595)
  - Law Training Fellowship Program - Administration, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 596)
  - Law Training Fellowship Program File - Murat Seker, 1981-1983 (Box 61, Folder 597)
  - International Communication Agency - Fulbright, 1979-1981 (Box 61, Folder 598-599)
  - Islam, Ethnicity, and the State in Afghanistan, Iran, and Pakistan Conference - Papers, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 600, Box 62, Folder 601-604)
  - Informal Sector of the Economy in the Middle East and North Africa Workshop - Papers, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 605, Box 63, Folder 606-607)
  - Gutman Killoran, Moira - Near and Middle East International Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 608)
  - Powell, Eve - Near and Middle East International Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral Award (Box 63, Folder 609)
  - Tamari, Stephen - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral Award, 1990-1992 (Box 63, Folder 610)
  - Cohen, Shaul - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 611)
  - Reimer, Michael - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 612)
  - Vitalis, Robert - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 63, Folder 613)
  - Michael Fischbach - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1989 - Predoctoral Award, 1988-1991 (Box 63, Folder 614)
  - Gelvin, James - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1989 - Predoctoral Award, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 615)
  - Celik, Zeynep - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1992 - Postdoctoral Award, 1991-1994 (Box 64, Folder 616)
  - Stetkeyvych, Suzanne - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1992 - Postdoctoral Award, 1992-1995 (Box 64, Folder 617)
  - Peirce, Leslie - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1992 - Postdoctoral Award, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 618)
  - Beinin, Joel - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1992 - Postdoctoral Award, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 619)
  - Kasaba, Resat - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1992 - Postdoctoral Award, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 620)
  - Butovsky, Avriel - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral Award, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 621)
  - Hajjar, Lisa - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral Award, 1991-1995 (Box 64, Folder 622)
  - Menicucci, Garay - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1991 - Predoctoral, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 623)
  - Dunne, Bruce - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1992 - Predoctoral Award, 1992-1994 (Box 64, Folder 624)
  - Goodman, Jane - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1992 - Predoctoral Award, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 625)
  - Murphy, Richard - Near and Middle East Research Fellowship 1992 - Predoctoral Award, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 626)
  - Salamandra, Christa - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1992 - Predoctoral Award, 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 627)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth - Near and Middle East Dissertation Fellowship 1992 - Predoctoral Award, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 628)
  - Combs-Schilling, Elaine - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 629)
  - Messick, Brinkley - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 630)
  - Swedenburg, Theodore - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991- Postdoctoral Award (Box 65, Folder 631)
  - Zeidenstein, Darrow - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1991 - Postdoctoral Award, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 632)
  - Tucker, Judith - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1990 - Postdoctoral Award, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 633)
  - Hillman, Michael - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1990 (Box 65, Folder 634)
  - Abu-Lughod, Lila - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 635)
  - Green, Arnold - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1989-1995 (Box 65, Folder 636)
  - Abrahamian, Ervand - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 637)
  - Micklewright, Nancy - Near and Middle East Advanced Research Grant 1989 - Postdoctoral Award, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 638)